Norkhairunnisa binti Juhari Kangsar

No 6, Lorong Sungai Isap Damai 18, 25150 Kuantan, Pahang.

(+6) 014 – 325 3302 khairunnisa.9131@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam,

Application for the Available Position

I would like to apply for a vacancy that is relevant to my qualifications in your esteemed organization. It will be my honor to serve the organization in achieving its goals and objectives.

As you can see, I have had experience in office environment, the retail sectors and service industry giving me varied skills and the ability to work with many different types of people. I believe I could fit easily into your team.

I am very enthusiastic and believe in experiencing new things. I am flexible, quick to pick up new skills and eager to learn from others. I also believe that mistakes are meant for learning not for repeating. I have high cultural competence which will prove useful to any company that gives attention to interpersonal communication. I addition, I managed a lot of events that have equipped me with great skills and criteria such as people skill, punctuality (time management), meticulous, organized and problem-solving.

I have excellent reference/s and would be delighted to discuss any possible vacancy with you at your convenience. I can be contacted through my e-mail khairunnisa.9141@gmail.com or via handphone at +60143253302. The enclosed resume provides you further details of my qualification and experiences. I am looking forwards to hearing from you soon.

I appreciate your kind consideration.

Thank you in advance.

Yours sincerely *Khairunnisa*



NORKHAIRUNNISA BINTI JUHARI KANGSAR

No 6, Lorong Sungai Isap Damai 18,

25150 Kuantan. Pahang.

Mobile: +6014 - 3253302

E-mail: khairunnisa.9131@gmail.com

PROFILE

A graduate with a major in English for Professional Communication and minor in Business, with knowledge on pragmatic, linguistic and professional communication. Also has a full Diploma in Public Administration and Policy Study. Team player, creative, energetic, enthusiastic, highly motivated and always on the go to experience new things. Organized and systematic, always learn from mistake, an optimist, pleasant personality and capable of building new relationships with stakeholders from different backgrounds. Has positive minds and ways to manage a group or individual task.

SKILLS

LANGUAGE

- Excellent command of Bahasa Malaysia and English
- Intermediate knowledge of Korean
- Presenting, copywriting, creative writing
- Cultural competency (experienced direct interaction with student from Korea and Japan)

COMPUTER LITERACY

Microsoft office, Basic knowledge in Website development (Adobe Dreamweaver); Graphic Design (Adobe Photoshop, SWISHmax); Video Editing (Window Movie Maker, Sony Vegas)

LEADERSHIP CAPABILITIES

Main Secretary of Kolej Kediaman Teratai, UiTM Shah Alam

Organized and handled Teratai residential college events and activities, keep documents organized, keep minutes of meetings for the organization.

Secretary for PALAPES UiTM Shah Alam

Organized and handled organization events and activities, keep documents organized, keep minutes of meetings for the organization, direct liase with the upper management of the organization.

EXPERIENCES

PART TIME ENGLISH HOME TUITION TEACHER

Giving English classes for student who going to take their PT3 or SPM exams. Essay writing, grammar and sentence structure.

RETAIL & MANAGEMENT, NDA TRAINING CONSULTANCY & NDA COMMUNICATION TRAINING, (SEPTEMCE – NOVEMBER 2014)

Intern – in charge of the incoming and outgoing stock of the company. Arrange and organized company filing system. Helped out with the company profile making and documents translations. Helped out with the company upgrading on the layout of their facebook page. Helped out with organizing events.

SECTOR FOCUSED CAREER FAIR 2013 (NOVEMBER 2013)

Volunteer – A career fair involving big organizations such as PETRONAS, Shell, MSC, PWT, etc.

SEKOLAH MENEGAH KEBANGSAAN SUNGAI ISAP (JUNE 2012 - FEBRUARY 2013)

Part time kitchen helper – Learned and assist the process of food making in the kitchen. Assist the buying and selling process of the students in time for them to purchased their lunch. Needed high level of patience, soft skills and good communication skills to interact with the customer.

FOOD RETAILER (JULY 2011 – AUGUST 2011)

Nasi lemak seller – In charge of the selling of nasi lemak for residential block at UiTM Lendu Melaka. Good communication skills and soft skills in order to convince the buyer to buy nasi lemak for late night snack. Go from one level to another and one block to another block.

FOOD BOOTH HELPER (JULY 2011 – AUGUST 2011)

Booth helper – Assist with the drink making process. Good communication skills with the customer.

PARKSON MALL (JANURY 2009 – MARCH 2009)

Part-time promoter – Responsible for the selling of a cloth brand. Good communication skills in assisting the customer in looking for the suitable piece that they desire and making purchase. Soft skills in assisting and negotiating with the customer in case that their needed design were not available in stock.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2015

Academy of Language Studies

Bachelor of Applied Lang. Studies (Hons.) English for Professional Communication

Final CGPA: 3.19

2009 - 2011

Faculty of Public Administration and Policy Study

Diploma in Public Administration and Policy Studies

Final CGPA: 2.78

OTHER AWARDS & ACTIVITIES

2014 Exco member of Summer School for Korean Students

Exco member of Summer School for Japanese Students

Event Manager for Teratai Residential students event

Exco for Teratai Paintball Challenge 2014

Participated for Teratai Paintball Challenge 2014 (Teratai College Representative)

Participated in hockey (for women) for Sukan Antara Kolej Kediaman

2013 Facilitator at Astin College for English Day

Participated for Teratai Paintball Challenge 2013 (Teratai College Representative)

Representative for Teratai Residential College for Archery Tournament in Jengka, Pahang

Participated in hockey (for women) for Sukan Antara Kolej Kediaman

Participated in Voice Out (Runner Up)

2012 Committee member of Teratai Block Representative

Secretary for PALAPES Shah Alam

Commissioned as Young Officer of Askar Wataniah (ROTU) at UUM Sintok.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Able to work under pressure to meet datelines
- Able to adapt to any surroundings and work with all kinds of people
- Able to lead and be lead
- Able to work independently with less supervision

REFERENCES

Dr.Rachel Burke Lecturer School of Education The University of Newcastle, Australia (02) 4921 6707 rachel.burke@newcastle.edu.au

Assoc Professor Dr Bernadette Foo English Department Academy of Language Studies UiTM Shah Alam Malaysia (+60) 12 6618608

^{*}Other references will be available upon request.